{
    "wkyu4sz": {
        "slider": [
            {
                "incorrectAnswers": 1,
                "endTime": 1716399646,
                "sessionLength": 3.52303,
                "correctAnswers": 0,
                "answersAndQuestions": [
                    {
                        "clickedAnswer": "46",
                        "responseTime": 3.407,
                        "correct": false,
                        "question": "4 x 8 = ?"
                    }
                ],
                "settings": {
                    "standardReinforcement": true,
                    "isMathMult": true,
                    "moderate": true,
                    "increaseSpawningRateExponential": true,
                    "isQuestionPosed": true,
                    "dropSpeedFast": true,
                    "isSpeedIncreasing": true,
                    "increaseSpeedRateExponential": true,
                    "isSplatImages": true
                },
                "startTime": 0.835
            },
            {
                "incorrectAnswers": 14,
                "endTime": 1716399837,
                "sessionLength": 59.7553878,
                "correctAnswers": 13,
                "answersAndQuestions": [
                    {
                        "responseTime": 2.534,
                        "correct": true,
                        "question": "12 x 5 = ?",
                        "clickedAnswer": 60
                    },
                    {
                        "responseTime": 1.694,
                        "correct": true,
                        "question": "3 x 10 = ?",
                        "clickedAnswer": 30
                    },
                    {
                        "responseTime": 2.846,
                        "correct": false,
                        "question": "9 x 4 = ?",
                        "clickedAnswer": "68"
                    },
                    {
                        "responseTime": 2.078,
                        "correct": true,
                        "question": "3 x 11 = ?",
                        "clickedAnswer": 33
                    },
                    {
                        "responseTime": 2.183,
                        "correct": true,
                        "question": "3 x 11 = ?",
                        "clickedAnswer": 33
                    },
                    {
                        "responseTime": 1.547,
                        "correct": true,
                        "question": "8 x 11 = ?",
                        "clickedAnswer": 88
                    },
                    {
                        "responseTime": 1.947,
                        "correct": true,
                        "question": "5 x 10 = ?",
                        "clickedAnswer": 50
                    },
                    {
                        "responseTime": 1.849,
                        "correct": true,
                        "question": "8 x 9 = ?",
                        "clickedAnswer": 72
                    },
                    {
                        "responseTime": 1.064,
                        "correct": false,
                        "question": "3 x 7 = ?",
                        "clickedAnswer": "122"
                    },
                    {
                        "responseTime": 1.116,
                        "correct": true,
                        "question": "6 x 4 = ?",
                        "clickedAnswer": 24
                    },
                    {
                        "responseTime": 1.861,
                        "correct": true,
                        "question": "4 x 12 = ?",
                        "clickedAnswer": 48
                    },
                    {
                        "responseTime": 2.487,
                        "correct": false,
                        "question": "3 x 8 = ?",
                        "clickedAnswer": "69"
                    },
                    {
                        "responseTime": 2.348,
                        "correct": false,
                        "question": "11 x 9 = ?",
                        "clickedAnswer": "51"
                    },
                    {
                        "responseTime": 2.928,
                        "correct": false,
                        "question": "12 x 7 = ?",
                        "clickedAnswer": "no-input"
                    },
                    {
                        "responseTime": 1.627,
                        "correct": true,
                        "question": "11 x 6 = ?",
                        "clickedAnswer": 66
                    },
                    {
                        "responseTime": 1.901,
                        "correct": false,
                        "question": "6 x 12 = ?",
                        "clickedAnswer": "134"
                    },
                    {
                        "responseTime": 2.068,
                        "correct": true,
                        "question": "3 x 9 = ?",
                        "clickedAnswer": 27
                    },
                    {
                        "responseTime": 2.921,
                        "correct": false,
                        "question": "5 x 5 = ?",
                        "clickedAnswer": "no-input"
                    },
                    {
                        "responseTime": 2.03,
                        "correct": false,
                        "question": "10 x 3 = ?",
                        "clickedAnswer": "104"
                    },
                    {
                        "responseTime": 2.014,
                        "correct": true,
                        "question": "7 x 3 = ?",
                        "clickedAnswer": 21
                    },
                    {
                        "responseTime": 1.498,
                        "correct": false,
                        "question": "7 x 12 = ?",
                        "clickedAnswer": "88"
                    },
                    {
                        "responseTime": 2.709,
                        "correct": false,
                        "question": "11 x 12 = ?",
                        "clickedAnswer": "no-input"
                    },
                    {
                        "responseTime": 2.604,
                        "correct": false,
                        "question": "6 x 4 = ?",
                        "clickedAnswer": "no-input"
                    },
                    {
                        "responseTime": 2.532,
                        "correct": false,
                        "question": "4 x 10 = ?",
                        "clickedAnswer": "no-input"
                    },
                    {
                        "responseTime": 1.512,
                        "correct": true,
                        "question": "9 x 9 = ?",
                        "clickedAnswer": 81
                    },
                    {
                        "responseTime": 2.496,
                        "correct": false,
                        "question": "3 x 7 = ?",
                        "clickedAnswer": "no-input"
                    },
                    {
                        "responseTime": 2.42,
                        "correct": false,
                        "question": "7 x 4 = ?",
                        "clickedAnswer": "no-input"
                    }
                ],
                "settings": {
                    "standardReinforcement": true,
                    "isMathMult": true,
                    "moderate": true,
                    "isQuestionPosed": true,
                    "increaseSpawningRateExponential": true,
                    "isSplatImages": true,
                    "dropSpeedFast": true,
                    "isSpeedIncreasing": true,
                    "increaseSpeedRateExponential": true
                },
                "startTime": 60.426
            }
        ]
    }
}